* 

Yidio Privacy Policy
====================

This Privacy Policy applies to information we collect about you at [https://www.yidio.com/](https://www.yidio.com/ "Yidio") (the "Website") and Yidio applications and how we use this information.  
  
**Collection of your Yidio Information**  
  
Your "Yidio information" includes certain technical information gathered or received when you use Yidio. Some of the technical information that may be collected or received includes: the type of browser you are using (e.g., Netscape, Internet Explorer), the type of operating system you are using (e.g., Windows or Mac OS), CPU type, your manner of connecting to the Internet (e.g., connection speed through narrowband or broadband access); Internet protocol address; Apps Installed; information about the version of service from an affiliate that you used prior to registering with the service; other information about your geographic location; and the domain name of your Internet service provider.  
  
While registering to use most of the Yidio services is not required, there are a limited number of optional services (for example, saving a video list) that require an "account". Registration functionality for Yidio is provided by the Yidio Network. If you choose to "Register an Account", you will need to register with and provide information to Yidio. You will then obtain a Screen Name or other credential issued by Yidio (collectively, "Screen Name") in order to access and use these optional services, and your Screen Name and associated services account will be subject to the Yidio Terms of Service Agreement and Privacy Practices indicated in your registration process.  

**How Your Yidio information is Used**  
  
Your Yidio information is used  

* to operate and improve the websites, services and offerings available through Yidio;
* to personalize the content provided to you;
* to fulfill your requests for products, programs, and services;
* to communicate with you and respond to your inquiries;
* to conduct research about your use of Yidio; and
* to help offer you other products, programs, or services that may be of interest.

Your Yidio information will not be shared with third parties unless it is necessary to fulfill a request, in other circumstances in which you have consented to the sharing of your Yidio information, or except as described in this Privacy Policy. We may use your Yidio information to present offers to you on behalf of business partners and advertisers. These business partners and advertisers may receive aggregate data about groups of Yidio users, but do not receive information that personally identifies you.  
  
If you use our communications tools to disclose information about yourself publicly (for example, by making your screen name and/or video lists publicly available), other online users may obtain access to any information you provide. The contents of your online communications, as well as other information about you as a Yidio user, may be accessed and disclosed in response to legal process (for example, a court order, search warrant or subpoena); in other circumstances in which we believe Yidio is being used in the commission of a crime; when we have a good faith belief that there is an emergency that poses a threat to the safety of you or another person; or when necessary either to protect our rights or property or the rights or property of our affiliated providers, or for us to render the service you have requested. We may use agents and contractors in order to help operate the service. If such agents and contractors have access to your Yidio information, they are required to protect this information in a manner that is consistent with this Privacy Policy by, for example, not using the information for any purpose other than to carry out the services they are performing for Yidio.  
  
In the event that ownership of us or the Yidio service was to change as a result of a merger, acquisition or transfer to another company, your Yidio information may be transferred. If such a transfer results in a material change in the use of your Yidio information, we will provide notice about the choices you have to decline to permit such a transfer.  
  
**Your Choices About Your Information**  
  
If you want to change your account information (for example, your Screen Name) you will need to log onto Yidio and access your account through the forum. Your access to your account information and choice will be governed by the Yidio policies.  
  
If you would like to delete your account, you can do so here: [https://www.yidio.com/user\_account\_delete.php](https://www.yidio.com/user_account_delete.php)  
  
**Cookies, Web Beacons and Similar Technologies**  
  
Cookies are text files that are placed in your computer's browser, and that can be used to help recognize you as a Yidio user. Web beacons are small pieces of code placed on Web pages that can be used, among other things, to count the users who visit that Web page, or to deliver a cookie to the browser of a user viewing that page. You can control cookies through your browser's settings. If you reject all cookies, however, you will not be able to take advantage of certain Yidio offerings.  
  
We may use cookies, web beacons or similar technologies in combination with your Yidio information to enhance and personalize your experience on Yidio, including to operate and improve offerings through Yidio; to help authenticate you when you use Yidio; to remember your preferences; to present and help measure and research the effectiveness of Yidio offerings and advertisements; and, to customize the content and advertisements provided to you through Yidio.  
  
Yidio and its advertisers may use advertising network providers to help present advertisements on Yidio. These advertising networks may use cookies, web beacons, or similar technologies on your computer in order to provide targeted advertisements about goods and services that may be of interest to you while visiting other Web sites. The use of cookies, web beacons, or similar technologies by ad network providers is subject to their own privacy policies. Any choices that you have about these technologies will be presented here in the event we utilize the services of any advertising network provider. Therefore, you are encouraged to return to this section periodically for updated information about advertising networks.  
  
Third party vendors, including Google, show your ads on sites on the internet. Third party vendors, including Google, use cookies to serve ads based on a user’s prior visits to your website. Users may opt out of Google’s use of cookies by visiting the [Google advertising opt-out page](https://www.google.com/privacy/ads/). (Alternatively you can opt out of a third party vendor’s use of cookies by visiting the [Network Advertising Initiative opt out page](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp).)  
  
We may use third-party advertising companies to collect data and/or serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, visit http://networkadvertising.org/.  
  
We use the personal information we collect in connection with providing you our services to detect and prevent fraudulent activity. We share this information with a third-party service provider to assist us with this effort.  
  
**Security**  
  
We have established safeguards to help prevent unauthorized access to or misuse of your Yidio information, but cannot guarantee that this information will never be disclosed in a manner inconsistent with this Privacy Policy (for example, as a result of unauthorized acts by third parties that violate applicable law or the policies of the service and its affiliated providers).  
  
**Special Note for Parents**  
  
Yidio is intended for a general audience. Registration for certain services on Yidio may not be available for children under the age of 13.  
  
**California Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance**  
  
Because we value your privacy we have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. We therefore will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your consent. As part of the California Online Privacy Protection Act, all users of our site may make any changes to their information at anytime by logging your user account page https://www.yidio.com/user\_account.php.  
  
**How to Contact Us**  
  
If you have any questions or concerns about Yidio's Privacy Policy or its implementation, you may contact us by going to the following link: [https://help.yidio.com/support/tickets/new](https://help.yidio.com/support/tickets/new "Contact Us").  
You may opt out of Yidio Emails here:: [https://www.yidio.com/user\_alerts.php](https://www.yidio.com/user_alerts.php).  
  
**Changes to this Privacy Policy and Additional Information**  
  
We may update this Privacy Policy from time to time, and so you should review this Policy periodically. If there are significant changes to Yidio's information practices, you will be provided with appropriate online notice. You may be provided other privacy-related information in connection with your use of offerings from Yidio, as well as for special features and services not described in this Policy that may be introduced in the future.  

### Common ID Cookie

This site uses cookies and similar tracking technologies such as the Common ID cookie to provide its services. Cookies are important devices for measuring advertising effectiveness and ensuring a robust online advertising industry. The Common ID cookie stores a unique user id in the first party domain and is accessible to our ad partners. This simple ID that can be utilized to improve user matching, especially for delivering ads to iOS and MacOS browsers. Users can opt out of the Common ID tracking cookie by clicking [here](#opt-out).

### Advertising Privacy Settings

FOR EU USERS ONLY: When you use our site, pre-selected companies may access and use certain information on your device and about your interests to serve ads or personalized content. You may revisit or change consent-choices at any time by clicking [here](#cmp).

* © 2024 Yidio LLC
